# **Anna Lise Arvelo**

Creative Thinker - Team Facilitator - Technical Project Manager 917-618-1601 <a href="mailto:annalise@mac.com">annalise@mac.com</a>

ST	TT	<b>/</b> T1	۱/T	A	D	<b>T</b> 7
51	11	/	VI	А	к	Y

Versatile Project Manager with over 15 years experience leading diverse teams to articulate measurable goals, remove impediment, and maximize success. Former professional actress and career coach dedicated to addressing needs of companies and individuals by creating agile plans, and writing specific user stories. Service-centric and cross-functional collaborator focused on client satisfaction, corporate retention, and overall team wellness. Advanced communicator.

#### **SKILLS**

Stakeholder management Coaching, training & instruction Web Design (Wix, SquareSpace, Word Press) Software Development Management Basic Coding Experience Learning Management Systems (LMS)
Talent development
Adult learning principles
Agile and predictive methodology
Visual Training Creation (PowerPoint, Google Slides, etc)

### **EDUCATION and TRAINING**

Thinkful, Inc.

Technical Project Management Intensive, expected completion April 2021

- Implemented hybrid, waterfall, or agile methodology to effectively deliver high-quality projects.
- Identified and created documents necessary for project management from planning to delivery.

Davidson College | Davidson, NC

Bachelor of Arts: Theatre Major, Eastern Religion Minor

#### EXPERIENCE

#### **Motivational and Career Coach**

An Actor Is Prepared: AnnaLiseJensen.com | New York, NY / Miami, FL | 07/2008 - Current

- Coach various audiences in private and group settings, supporting individual transitions to education programs and / or professional goals
- Tackle individual problems and limitations, helping clients design and implement strategies to achieve measurable success.
- Utilize agile methodology to create SMART goals during job search or career development
- Train individuals in public speaking, interviewing, and negotiation including navigating corporate structures, branding, and marketing functions.

#### **Adjunct Faculty**

New World School of the Arts | Miami, FL | 08/2016 - Current

- Formulate new curriculum for all classes, improving student learning by defining and articulating learning outcomes including performance metrics and measurements.
- Prepare recommendation letters for students pursuing job opportunities and internships.

# **Lead Remote Stylist & Coach**

Bombfell | New York, NY | 08/2015 - 02/2019

- Offered expert consulting services to a wide range of clients to support individual personal, style, and career goals.
- Boosted client satisfaction by quickly and effectively addressing complaints, delivering quality solutions.
- Coached and coordinated talented team of remote stylists committed to customer satisfaction.
- Positively impacted bottom-line profits through procedural streamlining, working collaboratively with buying and sales teams to achieve and surpass sales goals.

#### **Northeast Account Executive**

Juice Beauty | New York, NY | 05/2012 - 06/2014

- Managed and serviced 90+ accounts in Ulta, Whole Foods/Whole Body, and boutique stores and spas throughout NYC Metro, NY State, Connecticut, Pennsylvania, and New Jersey.
- Trained, led, and supported a team of ten freelancers working across four states.
- Elevated brand awareness and fuelled sale of Juice Beauty product, increasing store buy-in and maintaining consistency in brand representation across all stores in the region (337% Q4 2012 profits achieved).
- Created and managed financial reports, schedule, cost, resources, and risks

#### **PROJECTS**

# Page to Stage presents The Secret Garden: Savannah Repertory Theatre

• On-going project with the goal to present free copies of the novel The Secret Garden to 5000 fifth graders in the Savannah Public School.

#### Technical Project Management: XYZ Company Website

- Oversaw all planning and execution of project requirements.
- Ensured all project deliverables were functional and accepted by the client.

## Standards Based Curriculum Development

VIPKid, Inc - New World School of the Arts - Hands On! NYC - Area Stage Company

#### **PASSION PROJECTS**

United Community Options of South Florida: Director: Summer Theatre Camp Production

• Wrote, coached, and directed 35 young adults (ages 13-25) with Cerebral Palsy for a fully memorized and costumed performance of Peter Pan, presented for friends and family.

# **College Admissions Coaching**

- Assist students and family in choosing potential secondary education options
- Create a strategic agile-waterfall hybrid plan for academic applications, creative arts supplemental materials, and scholarship submissions
- Edit and approve the student's submissions for narrative